terapeak.com 2011-06-15

# Privacy Statement | Terapeak

## Last Updated: August 11, 2010

AERS Inc. a British Columbia company, is committed to protecting the privacy of users to this Website and for users of our on-line services in accordance with the requirements of Canadian federal and provincial privacy laws.

**AERS Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with[TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. This privacy statement covers the Websites [http://terapeak.com](http://www.terapeak.com/) and [http://analytics.terapeak.com](http://analytics.terapeak.com/) (the "Website"). The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at 250.483.3273. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). **

This privacy statement details how AERS Inc. collects and uses personal information from users of the Website or our on-line services and outlines our privacy commitment to you, the user, as well as our privacy practices. AERS Inc. wants all users of Terapeak.com to understand the purposes and uses for our collection of personal user information and we want to ensure that AERS Inc. has your consent to continue to collect, use and disclose your personal information for those purposes and uses as set out below.

At the same time, AERS Inc. wants its privacy statement to meet the highest commercial standards that establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices.

We want this Website and our on-line services to demonstrate our commitment to its user’s privacy, and we want you to know what our information and privacy practices are with respect to the following matters:

  1. What personally identifiable information AERS Inc. collects
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Website
  3. What organization collects the personal information
  4. How AERS Inc. uses the personal information
  5. With whom AERS Inc. may share user information
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the personal information
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under AERS Inc. control
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the personal information

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Anthony Sukow at the following email: [anthony[at]aers[dot]ca](https://web.archive.org/contact/anthony/aers/ca). If a user does not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact AERS Inc. directly with the following contact number: [250.483.3273](tel: 1 250 483 3273)

### Information Collection and Use of Information Collected

With the exception of any third party information arising from utilization of data sets, such as eBay data and shared eBay user information, AERS Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on the Website. AERS Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at the Website and may receive personally identifiable information from eBay and PayPal users who access the Website from links via eBay and PayPal.

If you use our on-line products and services, we ask you for:

  1. your name
  2. email address
  3. mailing address
  4. telephone number

By providing this information to AERS directly to the Website or links via eBay or PayPal and accessing and using our on-line products and services, you are expressly consenting to our use of this personally identifying information. This information is collected automatically and stored upon filling in the login information. In the event that you wish to opt out of our use of personally identifying information, do not complete the login information or use the opt out procedure set out below. AERS does not sell, rent or distribute any personally identifying information regarding any user to any third party, nor does AERS disclose lists of users to any third party except as described in this privacy policy (see "Business Transitions"). AERS does not solicit or facilitate the solicitation of any third party of any users as a result of their affiliation or status as a member or user of a specific data set. AERS does not spam or otherwise send unsolicited communications to users that are not reasonably related to our Website and online products and services.

The collection of such personally identifying information is limited to information reasonably related to the provision of AERS' online products and services. This information allows us to ensure that you are able to access and use our on-line products and services and for us to contact you regarding these service offerings.

### Testimonials

We receive permission to post testimonials that include personally identifiable information prior to posting to our site.

### **BLOG**

**If you use the blog on this Website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of the blog, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in the blog.**

In addition you may have chosen to be billed using PayPal or credit card services offered by Beanstream, who may ask for additional information to set up your accounts. We encourage you to review their privacy policies.

### User Password

In order for users to use some aspects of this Website, the user can choose unique identifiers such as a login and password. The username is related to the users email address. We use this login and password to track the activities of users and to contact the user about services on our site.

### Login

In order to use this Website, a user must first log in. During log in process, a user is required to give contact information such as email address and password. We use this information to contact the user to verify their contact information and for the purposes of setting up a client account, thereby allowing the user to access services on our site for which he/she wishes to participate. The user is also assigned unique identifiers such as username and password in order to fully utilize our site.

### Billing

For billing purposes we request the following information - (m) refers to mandatory, (o) refers to optional information.

### User:

### Personal Information

  1. e-mail address(m)
  2. password (m)
  3. first name (m)
  4. last name(m)
  5. phone number (m)
  6. address (o)

The decision by users not to complete the optional information may affect their full usability of the Terapeak.com Website.

We do not collect or request social insurance or social security numbers and do not retain credit card information in a database as billing information is processed through a credit card processor or PayPal. Contact information, such as business address and email address from the user are used for billing purposes or if there are issues with billing, the information is used to contact the user.

We may disclose personal information if legally required to do so such as to protect our rights and property, take emergency action regarding personal safety or where required by operation of law. We will advise the user in the event that such action is necessary.

### Information Use

We collect and use the personally identifying information, contact information and account information to process and deliver our online services, to facilitate the services requested by the user, to improve the services and features of the Website, to customize our services or delivery of information to you on the Website to make the use of the Website more effective and efficient, to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems and enforce this privacy statement. We automatically track certain information based on the user's use of our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our user's demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand the users and our client base. We track information regarding the URL that the user came from (whether from our site or not), which URL the user may go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), and what browser is being used and the user's IP address. We collect information to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use only. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information. Personal identity is kept anonymous. We collect and use information from messages, and users who choose to post information on our site. We also collect and use personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website.

We collect and use information if users register for Terapeaks Website or another third party Website or use a third party Website providing a service for the Terapeak Website that helps facilitate a user's activity on Terapeak’s Website and that third party Website may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to Terapeak’s Website AERS Inc. does not sell or rent any information collected from users to other third parties.

We create user accounts to tailor the information displayed to each individual user and as applicable to the users.

The Website has specific sections available to all users and other specific sections that may be accessed by members only.

### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Website and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while a user is on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Once users close the browser for the session ID cookie, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

We use cookies on certain pages of our site to help analyze our Website flow, measure promotional effectiveness and promote trust and safety. We offer certain features that are available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies may also be used in the future to help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. A user is always free to decline our cookies if their browser permits, although in declining a cookie, you may not be able to use certain features of our Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

Some of our business partners may use cookies and Web beacons on our site, for example a tracking utility company. However, we have no access to or control over these tracking technologies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies or Web beacons for advertising and our internal tracking purposes.

We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) information and provide information in a non-personally identifiable manner to other third party marketing partners.

This privacy statement covers the use of tracking technologies by [www.terapeak.com](http://www.terapeak.com/ "www.terapeak.com") only and does not cover the use of tracking technologies by any third parties.

### Log Files

Like most standard Website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information such as your email address.

### Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a welcoming email. Established members will only receive information on products, services, special deals, in a once monthly newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications (a user can opt out of the newsletter in our "profile" section). You may also unsubscribe by following the instructions included in each promotional email.

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections of the Terapeak.com Website to opt out of receiving these types of communications.

### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We reply via email or phone, in accordance to the users wishes.

### Sharing

### Legal Disclaimer

With the exception of user obligations arising from existing relationships with eBay and use of eBay services that may result in shared user information, and although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website.

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers.

### Third Party Advertisers

We do not share Website usage information about users with third party advertisers.

### Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties

We DO NOT share personal information with third parties who are not service providers.

### Third Party Intermediaries

We use outside credit card processing companies - PayPal and Beanstream - to bill users for services. Users are governed by terms and conditions of payment as set by PayPal or Beanstream. The PayPal or Beanstream payment window appears on the Terapeak.com Website. Please review their privacy policies for more information on their practices.

### Service Providers

We partner with other third parties such as a tracking utility company and a live chat provider, to provide specific services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services and not for their own marketing purposes.

### Business Transitions

In the event that AERS Inc. goes through a business transition such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, personal user information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Website for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the user’s personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. We may disclose personal information of a user to an agent when in the reasonable judgment of AERS Inc. the individual is seeking information as an agent of the user.

Subject to applicable regulatory requirements, we may disclose personal information of a user to a credit reporting agency.

We may disclose personal information of a user to a public agency when in the reasonable judgment of AERS Inc., there is imminent danger to person or property to which such disclosure would avoid or minimize the danger.

### Choice/Opt-out

We do not use our user’s information for purposes unrelated to our site. We would like to continue to have the user's consent for the purposes and uses of personal information as set out in this privacy statement, however, you as a user may choose to refuse or withdraw your consent by refusing to give us personal information or withdrawing such consent subject to any applicable contractual or notice provisions by emailing us at [support[at]terapeak[dot]com](https://web.archive.org/contact/support/terapeak/com).

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following instructions given in the footer of the email or emailing [support[at]terapeak[dot]com](https://web.archive.org/contact/support/terapeak/com).

### Links

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AERS Inc., is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

### Surveys & Contests

From time to time our site requests information from users via internal or in-house surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as postal or zip code). Contact information will be used to notify winners and award prizes and shared with the contest and survey sponsors. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the user experience within the Website. User’s personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties as all surveys and contests are internal and or in-house.

### Security

This Website takes every precaution to protect our user’s information. When users submit sensitive information via the Website, their information is protected both online and off-line. All payments are handled through PayPal or Beanstream.

We protect personal information and the user's right to privacy by:

  1. Only collecting personal information for the purposes set out in this privacy statement
  2. Ensuring appropriate security measures are in place
  3. Ensuring appropriate confidentiality measures are in place for personal information when dealing with third party
  4. Ensuring that personal information is kept up to date and current for the purposes in which it is being used
  5. Honoring any user request for access to their personal information

When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information such as credit card number, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as a registration form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line for all of our user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every time new policies are added, our employees are notified and reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can to do to ensure our user’s information is protected.

### Supplementation of Information

In order for this Website to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

### Credit Card

We do not conduct credit card validation as all credit card processing for our products and services is undertaken by PayPal or Beanstream.

### Purchasing History

We do not combine information about the purchasing habits of our users with other third parties.

### Enhancement of Marketing Profile

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as name, postal code, zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate user’s personally identifiable information. This can be done by going to the account page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support[at]terapeak[dot]com](https://web.archive.org/contact/support/terapeak/com).

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy statement and or practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. The posting of changes to the privacy statement shall be effective within 30 days of post.

If we are going to use personally identifiable user information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users delete/deactivate their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Website notifying users of the change. In cases where we post a notice we will also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, to notify them of the changes in our privacy practices.

### Contact Information

If users have any questions, concerns or suggestions regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at:

  * Phone: 250.483.3273
  * Fax: 250.483.3271
  * Email: [support[at]terapeak[dot]com](https://web.archive.org/contact/support/terapeak/com)
  * Website URL: www.terapeak.com

Otherwise, we assume that we have you - the user of our Website and or on-line services - consent to collect, use and disclose your personal information for the purposes and uses identified in this privacy statement.

For further information on the AERS Corporate Privacy Code, please email us at [support[at]terapeak[dot]com](https://web.archive.org/contact/support/terapeak/com).

2307-4464 Markham St.  
Victoria, BC  
V8Z 7X8
